http://cecourses.org/about/agreement/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice | Nursing Continuing Education CEU
Nursing Continuing Education CEU
Klimes Institute: Convenient Quality Health, Ethics, & Statistics CE coures 3hr/$21
Klimes Institute Report
Printing Your Certificate(s)
Klimes
Privacy Notice
CE Courses LLC, doing business as Klimes Institute, is committed to the confidentiality and trust with respect to the privacy of the personal information that we collect from you. Please read the following to understand privacy practices.
While on our sites, you may voluntarily provide information to Klimes Institute to utilize our continuing education services. The types of personal information collected may include:
Contact details including name, email address, physical address, and telephone number:
Usernames and passwords
Educational and professional background information
Payment information
Comments, posts and other content you submit
Communication preferences
Klimes Institute also collects and store information through a variety of automatic technologies, such as cookies (small text files sent to your computer), web beacons (clear or single pixel.gifs) and other technologies. The information collected from these automatic technologies is used to monitor usage and enhance the performance of the Service and is not shared or sold for commercial purposes. The information may be shared to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service, or as required by law.
When we request information from you on the Site, you may always choose to decline, but in doing so, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site. You can control cookies through browser settings or other tools, but if you block certain cookies, you may not be able to register, login, or make use of the full Service.
To administer the service, Klimes Institute may contract with third party affiliates and include links to other websites. Credit or debit card information to complete a transaction from our Service, may be collected directly by a payment processor and/or a fulfillment company on our behalf, but Klimes Institute does not record or store credit or debit card information. In cases where our provider partner may collect information from you directly, their Privacy Notice may apply to their use of your information. The Privacy Notice of our provider partner may differ from ours, and you should contact the provider partner for additional information.
All information gathered on our Site is stored within databases which only we and services provider are provided access. However, as effective as the reasonable security measures implemented by us may be, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our Site’s servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us.
If you have any questions regarding the Klimes Institute Privacy Notice please contact support@cecourses.org for additional information.
Klimes Institute may change this Privacy Notice from time to time and any changes will be posted on this page with an updated revision date.
Last Revised: 3/1/2018
Like this:Like Loading...
Need Support/Help? If you need help, have issues or have any questions, please email support@cecourses.org
Continuing Education for Nurses Klimes Institute provides easy to use, inexpensive, online Continuing Education courses 24/7/365 for Nurses and Healthcare Professionals.
California Board of Registered Nursing Approval Klimes Institute is approved as a CE provider by:
Deep Learning Learn beyond the minimum test requirements. Go deeper:
%d bloggers like this:
